Janice has a question. Who of the six of you...
我想问一个问题 你们当中有哪一个人
... has slept with who of the six of you?
跟你们当中的另一个人睡过？
Wow,it's like a dirty math problem.
好色的数学问题
I'm sorry,the answer there would be none of us.
很抱歉，答案是一个也没有
Over the years,none of you ever got drunk and stupid?
这几年下来 你们都没有喝醉做蠢事？
Well,that's really a different question.
那是另外一个问题
I can't believe a group of people who spends this much time together...
想不到一群成天混在一起的人
... has never bumped uglies.
居然没做过丑事
There was that one time Monica and Rachel got together.
摩妮卡曾经和瑞秋在一起
What?
什么？
Excuse me,there was no "time."
很抱歉，没有那回事
Okay,but let's say there was.
那就假设有
How might that go?
会怎么样？
Well then answer me this:
那就告诉我
Have any of you ever almost...?
你们有没有差一点…？
-Anybody need more coffee? -Hey,there's a dog out there!
还有谁要咖啡？ 外面有狗狗
The One With the Flashback
本集播出：“六人成行前”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
“三年前”
-That is so unfortunate. -What?
太可惜了？ 怎么了？
Cute Naked Guy's starting to put on weight.
可爱裸男越来越胖
I'll be back in just a minute.
我马上回来
I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks on the phone.
菲比，抱歉 我的口红印到电话筒了
You didn't leave lipstick marks on the phone.
你没有啊
Then it must have been you. Bye.
那就是你罗，再见
Bye-bye.
拜拜
-That's why I moved out. -Hey,while we're on that...
所以我才要搬走 说到这件事
...when are you gonna tell my sister you don't live here anymore?
你几时要告诉我老妹 你不住这里了？
On some level,she already knows.
在某些层面上，她已经知道了
She doesn't know you sneak out every night...
她并不知道你每天晚上溜出去
...and back every morning...
每天早上溜回来
...and that you've been at your grandmother's for a week.
而且已在你奶奶家住了一星期
Okay,well,maybe not on those levels.
好吧，也许不是这些层面
I'm never gonna find a roommate. Ever.
我永远也找不到室友
Nobody good?
没有好的人选？
There was the guy with the ferrets.
有个砘镅了一堆雪貂
That's plural.
是一堆喔
The spitter. And the guy who enjoyed my name so much...
有一个爱吐口水 还有一个觉得我的名字很好玩
... he made a noise every time he said it.
每次说到都要发出怪声
"Nice to meet you,Chandler Bing. Bing!"
幸会，钱德宾，宾！
"Great apartment,Chandler Bing. Bing!"
好棒的房子，钱德宾 宾！
-How many more tomorrow? -Two.
明天还有几个？ 两个
This photographer who seemed really dull...
一个好像很无趣的摄影师
...and this actor guy who I'm not sure about.
和一个怪怪的演员
When I answered the phone "Chandler Bing"...
我拿起电话说“钱德宾”
... he said,"Whoa! Short message!"
他居然说：哇，好短的留言
Foot on the floor or come over no more.
罗斯，脚放下 否则以后不准来
Your dresser is missing, but this she notices.
你的梳妆台都不见了 她只注意到这个
-What? -I have to go.
什么？ 我该走了
Carol should be home by now,so....
卡洛应该回家了，所以…
-How's it going with you guys? -Better,actually.
你们两个还好吗？ 有改善了
I finally figured out why we're having so much trouble.
我终于知道我们为何这么不顺
-Oh,really? -Yeah. You know how I have you guys?
真的？ 对，你们也知道我有你们
She doesn't have any close friends that are just hers.
她自己没有要好的朋友
But last week,she met this woman at the gym,"Susan" something.
不过上星期，她在健身房 认识一个叫苏珊的女人
And they really hit it off,and I think it's gonna make a difference.
她们一拍即合 这样一来就不一样了
So,Eric...
艾瑞克
...what kind of photography do you do?
你是哪一种摄影师？
Oh,mostly fashion.
大部份是流行时尚
There may be models here sometimes. I hope that's cool.
偶尔会有模特儿过来 没关系吧
Yes,that is cool.
没关系
Because I have models here, you know...
因为有模特儿来的机率…
... never.
是零
During the summer I spend most weekends at my sister's beach house...
这个夏天 我都到我姐的海边小屋度周末
...which you're welcome to use.
也欢迎你去玩
Although I should tell you, she's a porn star.
不过我得告诉你 她是演A片的
Well,I still have one more person to meet.
我还要见一个人
But unless it turns out to be your sister...
不过除非她是你姐姐…
... I think your chances are pretty good.
你的机会应该很大
All right.
好
Bedroom,bathroom,living room.
卧房、浴室、客厅
This here is the kitchen, and thanks for coming by. Bye-bye.
这里是厨房，谢谢你来 再见
Don't you wanna ask me any questions?
你不想问我问题吗？
Sure.
好…
What's up?
你好吗？
Well,I'm an actor.
我是演员
I'm fairly neat.
我很爱干净
I got my own TV.
我自己有电视
Oh,and don't worry,I'm totally okay with the gay thing.
你放心，我不排斥同性恋
What gay thing?
什么同性恋？
Just,you know,in general. The whole "people-being-gay" thing.
就是一般的同性恋的事
Totally cool with that.
我完全不在意
Okay,Jerry. Thanks for stopping by.
乔利，谢谢你来
Oh,my God!
（好帅！）
Hey,Mon.
老莫
-Wanna hear something that sucks? -Do I ever!
想听一件很烂的事吗？ 我听多了
-Chris says they're closing the bar. -No way!
克里斯要把酒吧收了 不会吧
They're turning it into a coffee place.
这里要改成一家咖啡店
Just coffee?
只卖咖啡？
-Where are we gonna hang out? -You got me.
我们以后要去哪里？ 我怎么知道
-Can I get a beer? -Did you pick a roommate?
一瓶啤酒 室友挑好了吗？
-You bet. -ls it the ltalian guy?
那当然 是那个意大利帅哥吗？
Yeah,right.
怎么可能
He's so cute.
他好可爱
That's what I want. A roommate I can walk around with...
我就是需要一个超帅室友
...and be referred to as "the funny one."
好被贬下去
Table's free. Rack them up. Back in a minute.
球台空了，准备一下 我马上回来
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
准备让我打屁股吧
Okay,but after that, we're shooting some pool.
好，不过之后要打球
Excuse me? Hello? Hi.
不对，很抱歉
My friend ordered an onion...
我朋友点的是洋葱
... not an olive.
不是橄榄
And I ordered a rum and Diet Coke...
我点的是糖蜜酒和健怡
...which I don't think this is.
这杯不是
-I am so sorry. -That's all right.
对不起 没关系
How hard is it to get a couple drinks right,huh?
准备饮料能有多难？
I would like to propose a toast...
我们来敬酒
...to the woman who,in one year from today,will become...
这位女士在一年后的今天 就要嫁给…
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Barber,D. D.S.
贝利巴柏医生，牙科博士
I think it's time to see the ring again.
应该再秀一次戒指了
Isn't it exciting? I mean, it's like having a boyfriend for life!
很棒吧？ 就好像一辈子都有男朋友
Yeah. I know.
是啊，我知道
What?
怎么了？
Oh,I don't know.
我不晓得
Well,maybe it's just the idea...
也许只是想到…
...of Barry for the rest of my life.
一辈子要跟贝利在一起
I don't know,I think l....
我不知道，我觉得…
I feel like having one last fling...
我想来个最后的放纵
...just to sort of get it out of my system.
好永远忘记这种事
-Rachel,stop! -You're so bad!
瑞秋，别说了 你好坏
I'm serious. I really think I need to just have...
我是褚的 我真的觉得我需要…
...some meaningless sex, you know?
毫无意义的性爱
With the next guy I see.
就跟下一个看到的男人
Excuse me,I seem to have dropped my ball.
抱歉，我的球好像掉了
Yeah,so?
所以呢？
And now I've picked it up again.
我又把它检起来了
My God! I went to high school with her.
天哪，那是我的高中同学
Look! Hi! What do you think?
你觉得如何？
Oh,my God!
天哪
You can't even see where the Titanic hit it.
连铁达尼都撞不坏它
Yes,his name is Barry. He's a doctor,thank you very much.
没错，他叫贝利 是一位医生
Just like you always wanted. Congratulations.
这是你的梦想，恭喜你
Thank you. So how about you? Are you seeing anybody?
谢谢 那你呢？有对象吗？
Not right now.
目前没有
Oh,well,that's okay.
没关系
I know.
我知道
So I think I'll get back to my friend.
我要去找我朋友了
Oh,yeah. Sure,sure,sure.
好…
Can we have lunch the next time I'm in the city?
下次我进城，我们一起吃饭？
That'd be great.
好啊
-Okay. -Thanks.
再见 再见
Ten bucks says I never see that woman again in my life.
我打赌这辈子都不会再见到她
No,honey,really. It's fine.
真的，没关系
Just...
你就…
...go with Susan.
跟苏珊去吧
Really,I think
真的，我觉得…
I think girls' night out is a great idea.
我觉得女生一起出门很好啊
Okay. Okay. Bye.
好…好，再见
-What are they doing? -I don't know. Something girly.
她们要做什么？ 不晓得，女生做的事
Hey,you're early.
你回来早了
What are you doing with the lamp?
你拿着那盏灯做什么？
Just taking it to get rewired.
拿去换电线
Don't take it where you took the stereo. They've had that over a week.
别送去修音响那一家 他们已经修了一星期
Mr. Heckles,no one is making any noise up here.
海克斯先生 我们没有制造噪音
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
你们打扰我练习双簧管了
-You don't play the oboe. -I could play the oboe.
你又不会吹双簧管 我可以吹
Then I'm gonna have to ask you to keep it down.
那就请你小声一点
Who are you?
你是谁？
-I'm Eric,Chandler's new roommate. -I'm Chandler's new roommate.
艾瑞克，钱德的新室友 我才是钱德的新室友
-I don't think so. -I could be Chandler's new roommate.
不是吧 我可以当钱德的新室友
-But he told me over the phone -He told me in person.
但是他打电话告诉我… 他是亲口告诉我的
That's weird.
好奇怪
I'm going to go into my new apartment now.
我要回我的新公寓了
Hi again.
又见面了
Thank you so much.
谢谢你
Don't thank me. Thank the jerk that never showed up.
别谢我，谢那个没出现的混蛋
Okay,I gotta get to work.
我要去上班了
-You want some help? -No,thanks. I got it.
需要帮忙吗？ 不用了，我可以
No,I don't!
我不行
You okay?
没事吧？
I stood up too fast. Got a little head rush.
我起来得太快了，头有点晕
It's the heat.
太热了
And the humidity.
而且又潮湿
That's...
加起来…
...a tough combination.
实在蛮难受的
Do you want to come in for some lemonade?
想不想进来喝杯柠檬汁？
Like you wouldn't believe.
想得不得了
This is a great place.
你家好漂亮
Thank you.
谢谢
Just make yourself comfortable.
不要客气
Gotcha.
懂了
So this place is really my grandmother's.
这其实是我奶奶的房子
I got it when she moved to Florida. Otherwise I could never afford it.
她搬去佛州，我才能住 否则我根本租不起
So if the landlord ever asks...
要是房东问起
... I'm an 87-year-old woman who's afraid of her VCR. You thirsty?
你就说我是87岁… 害怕录影机的老太太，你渴吗
You bet I am!
渴得不得了
Okay...
好
... here's your penis!
这是你的老二！
Oh,my God! What the hell are you doing?
天哪！你在干什么？
You said,"You wanna come in for some lemonade?"
你问我想不想进来喝柠檬汁
So?
所以呢？
Were you just gonna give me lemonade?
你只是要给我柠檬汁？ 是啊
Cover yourself up!
赶快遮起来！
Oh,right. Sorry.
对喔，抱歉
God,I don't believe this!
我真不敢相信
Someone asks you in for lemonade and that means they want to have sex?
人家请你喝柠檬汁 就是想跟你上床？
Usually,yeah. Well,not just lemonade.
通常是啊，不只柠檬汁啦
Iced tea,sometimes juice.
冰茶啦，果汁啦
Look,sorry. I just
我很抱歉，我只是…
I thought you liked me.
我以为你喜欢我
I'm such a jerk.
我真混蛋
It's okay.
没关系
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
任何人都会碰上这种事
Not anyone I know,but....
我不认识这种人，不过…
By the way,I can still see it.
我还是看得到
Where's your bed?
菲比，你的床呢？
It's not in the apartment?
不在屋里吗？
I can't believe this is happening again.
居然又发生这种事了
-What? -Okay,enough with the third degree!
什么？ 好，别拷问我了
I don't live here anymore.
我…我不住这里了
-What are you talking about? -I'm sorry.
你在说什么？ 对不起
I don't live here anymore.
我不住这里了
I didn't know how to tell you. But,you know,everybody else knows.
我不知道该怎么告诉你 但是其他人都知道
Everybody knows?
大家都知道？
That was supposed to be a good thing. I forget why.
这本来是好事 但是我忘了原因
Do you know I couldn't sleep for a month...
我曾经一整个月睡不着
...because I got a dot of ink on one of the sofa cushions?
就因为我在沙发垫上 滴了一滴墨水
You could've just turned the cushion over.
你可以把它翻面啊
I would have,but I had a spaghetti stain on the other side.
我本来会翻，但另一面 沾到意大利面酱汁
What?
什么？
This is what I'm talking about.
我就是这个意思
I need to live in a land where people can spill!
我要住在可以打翻东西的地方
Well,you can spill.
你可以打翻东西啊…
In the sink.
在水槽里
Oh,honey. It's not your fault, you know. This is who you are.
亲爱的，不是你不好 你就是这样
And I love you. And I want us to be friends.
我爱你，我要我们是朋友
And if I stay here, I don't see that happening.
要是我留在这里 那是不可能的
-I love you too. -Good.
我也爱你 那就好
What?
怎么了？
What? I'm just sad.
什么？我只是很难过
No,you're not. You're wondering which cushion it is.
才怪，你在想是哪一个垫子
So what are you watching?
在看什么？
Baywatch.
“海滩游侠”
What's it about?
在演什么？
Lifeguards.
救生员
Well,it sounds kind of stup
听起来蛮蠢…
Who's she?
她是谁？
Nicole Eggert.
妮可艾格
We like her.
她超辣的
Wow! Look at them run!
哇，她们在跑
They do that a lot.
她们经常在跑
Hey,you want a beer?
你要喝啤酒吗？
-I'll get one. -Don't get up. I got a cooler here.
我去拿 别起来，冰桶在这里
Do you have any beers? We're out of beers.
你有啤酒吗？我们喝完了
Help yourself.
自己拿
You okay?
你还好吗？
Phoebe moved out.
菲比搬走了
Right.
对
I don't understand.
我不懂
Am I so hard to live with? Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
我真的这么难相处？ 所以才找不到男朋友？
You don't have a boyfriend because....
不是，你没有男朋友是因为…
I don't know why you don't have a boyfriend.
我不知道为什么
You should have a boyfriend.
你应该要有的
I think so.
我也这么认为
Come here.
过来
来
Listen,you are one of my favorite people...
听我说 你是我最喜欢的人之一
...and the most beautiful woman I've ever known in real life.
还是我在现实中所认识 最漂亮的女人
Where is everybody?
人都在哪里？
It's already closed. Chris gave me the keys to lock up. What is wrong?
已经打烊了，克里斯要我锁门 出了什么事？
I think my marriage...
我想我的婚姻…
...is kind of over.
应该是完蛋了
Oh,no! Why?
不会吧，为什么？
Because Carol's a lesbian.
因为卡洛是女同性恋
And I'm not one.
而我不是女同性恋
And apparently it's not a mix-and-match situation.
而且这显然不是一时激情
Oh,my God!
天哪
I don't believe it!
我真不敢相信
Oh,you poor bunny.
可怜的孩子
I'm an idiot.
我是白痴
I mean,I should have seen it.
我早该看出来了
I mean,Carol and I would be out, and she'd see some beautiful woman...
卡洛和我出门 她都会看漂亮美眉
...and she'd be "Ross! Look at her!"
她会说：罗斯，你看她
And I'd think...
我还觉得…
... "God,my wife is cool."
天哪，我老婆真酷
Hey,do you think that Susan person is her lover?
你觉得那个苏珊 是她的情人吗？
Well,now I do!
我现在知道了
I'm sorry.
对不起
Seven years!
都七年了
I mean,we've been together seven years.
我们在一起七年了
She's the only woman who's ever loved me.
她是唯一爱过我的女人
She's the only woman I've ever....
也是我唯一有过…
This is nice.
真好
I know. It is,isn't it?
我知道，很棒对不对？
No,I mean it. This feels really good.
我是褚的，摸起来好舒服
Is it 100% cotton?
是百分之百纯棉吗？
And I got it on sale too.
对，而且还是特价品
I should go.
我该走了
One of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.
有一个救生员正要拆除核弹
If you want to get a drink later,we can.
我们待会可以去喝一杯
That sounds great.
听起来不错
Oh,and listen,it's gonna be
还有，不会有…
I know.
我知道
Thanks.
谢了
Maybe this wouldn't have happened if I'd been more nurturing...
搞不好可以避免 要是我再有深度一点
...or I'd paid more attention...
或是多注意她一点
...or I had a uterus.
或是我有子宫
-I can't believe it. -I know.
我真不敢相信 我知道
You know,you don't deserve this. You don't,Ross.
你不该受这种折磨，真的
-You're so good. -Thanks.
你人这么好 谢谢
And you're so sweet.
而且你很体帖
-Thanks. -And you're kind.
谢谢 心肠又好
Thanks.
谢谢
Come here.
过来
Wait,wait,wait.
等一下
It's okay.
别管了
Wait,wait,wait! My foot is stuck in the pocket.
等一下，我的脚卡在球洞里
-What? -I can't get it out.
什么？ 我弄不出来
That's not something a girl wants to hear.
女生可不想听到这种话
Come on,don't start.
你别逗我
What?
怎么了？
Stupid balls are in the way.
那些烂球好碍事
Oh,well.
好吧
That probably wouldn't have been the most constructive solution.
这不是最有建设性的解决方式
You have chalk on your face.
你的脸上有粉笔灰
You're right. I don't know why I always thought this was real grass.
你说得对 我怎么会以为这是真的草皮
Honey,you okay?
你还好吗？
My wife's a lesbian.
我老婆是同性恋
Cool!
酷！
Ross,Joey. Joey,Ross.
罗斯，乔伊，乔伊，罗斯
I can't believe you came back.
你竟然回来了
Don't say anything.
什么都不要说
I don't wanna speak. I don't wanna think.
我不想说话，我不想思考
I just want you to take me and kiss me and make love to me right here...
我只要你现在就吻我…
... right now.
跟我作爱
You missed the exit.
你错过交流道了
Sorry.
对不起
My God,what were you thinking about?
真是的，你在想什么？
Barry.
贝利